[
    {
        "question": "My Hometown is in _______.",
        "answers": ["Shenzhen", "Cai Xukun", "Huaihua", "Aberdeen"],
        "correct": "Huaihua"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which course I never skip?",
        "answers": ["Web Application Course"],
        "correct": "Web Application Course"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is my dream?",
        "answers": ["Become United States president", "Buy NASA", "Get Nobel Prize", "Become the headmistress of SCNU"],
        "correct": "Become the headmistress of SCNU"
    },
    {
        "question": "What I wanted to do in high school?",
        "answers": ["A teacher", "A biologist", "A singer", "A robot"],
        "correct": "A biologist"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many award I have got in programming competition?",
        "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "3"],
        "correct": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of crafts I recently like to do?",
        "answers": ["Plant beads", "Perler beads", "Cook beads"],
        "correct": "Perler beads"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of my favorite singerâ€™s concert?",
        "answers": ["I AM GLORY", "I AM GLOCERY", "I AM G.E.M.", "I AM GLORIA"],
        "correct": "I AM GLORIA"
    },
    {
        "question": "What game I am playing recently?",
        "answers": ["PUBG", "League of Legends", "Stardew Valley"],
        "correct": "Stardew Valley"
    },
    {
        "question": "What kind of sports do I most do well in?",
        "answers": ["Sprinting", "Marathon", "Sleeping"],
        "correct": "Sprinting"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following sports is NOT referred in my mastered sports?",
        "answers": ["Badminton", "Soccer", "Tennis", "Volleyball"],
        "correct": "Tennis"
    }
]
